Guide to the Stanford Unversity, Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Unversity, Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility, records
1993-2007
SC1199
Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility.
6 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-2014-081
  - United Nations, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CPSR Budgets, Expense Reports, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Donations and 2003 Annual Report, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CPSR Board of Directors Reference Manual, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1996-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - PDC 2002 Sweden (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - High Donors - CPSR, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chapter Formation Petitions, 1993-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Certificates of Life Membership, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bylaws of CPSR, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Budget for FY 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chapter Contacts, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Performance Review of Susan Evoy, June 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Conferences to Post, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - December 2006 Board Meeting and Budget for FY 2007, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CPSR Members Meeting Sign-In, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - CPSR Board, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Conferences, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - T-shirts and other memorabilia, undated (Box 1)